

PROFILE

I am an enthusiastic swimming coach with high aspirations for students, committed to supporting growth in children and enabling them to realize their learning objectives. Coaching was my passion. Diploma in Swimming has helped me gain more scientific knowledge on coaching.

I have endured 8 years of experience in coaching field. My love for coaching and teaching is demonstrated in my students' results; for the last three years, my students have participated at the nationals and won a number of state medals.

CONTACT

PHONE:

9581271722 / 9051283289

EMAIL

chilkaroychatterjee@gmail.com

SKILLS

Strong Command in Coaching Time management People management Coaching Dynamics

HOBBIES

Water polo Synchronized swimming Finn's swimming Physical conditioning Yoga

CHILKA

CHATTERJEE

Swimming Coach, B.P.Ed., NIS Patiala

EDUCATION

BCOM

West Bengal State University (3-year regular course)

BPED

Andhra University (2-year regular course)

NIS CERTIFIED COACH

NIS certified coach in 2016 from KIIT University, SAI (Ministry Of Sports And Youth Affairs).

DIPLOMA IN COACHING (NSNIS PATIALA)

Bangalore Centre, SAI (1-year regular course)

WORK EXPERIENCE

HEAD COACH - YMCA

YMCA women team, Kolkata 2013-15

OAKRIDGE INTERNATIONAL SCHOOL (HEAD COACH)

Worked in this IB school from 2016 to July 2017 at Visakhapatnam.

GD GOENKA PUBLIC SCHOOL (HEAD COACH)

Worked in this school from July 2017 to 2019 at Rajnagar Extension, Ghaziabad.

ACHIEVEMENTS

JUNIOR AND SENIOR NATIONAL MEDALIST

Represented state team from 2006 to 2012 winning medals for the team. Highest achievement is senior national **silver** medalist in 2012.

QUALIFIED LIFE GUARD

Won medals in senior championship in 2011 and 2012.

Represented India in life guard, world rescue championship in Melbourne, Australia.

LONG DISTANCE

19KM **third** In 2010.

OPEN SEA SWIMMING

Medalist In Open Sea Swimming at Mumbai In 2012.

ASSISTANT COACH - INDIAN TEAM

Worked as an assistant coach as an intern from NIS diploma trainees under Partha Pratim Majumder, Head Coach, Senior and junior Indian Swimming Team.